<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assessment on Educational Redesign Aid</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assessment on Educational Redesign Aid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What to do</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/what/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/what/</guid>
      <description>Appropriate assessment formats depend on a range of factors, including the subject matter, content complexity, course level and the number of students enrolled. Typically, they include essays, reports, presentations, skills tests, open-ended or multiple choice exams. We recommend that you review our Assessments Documentation to learn more about the digital varieties for each of the assignment and assessment options, and then determine what is most appropriate for your course. Here, you can also find information on when to run changes by your exam committee and how/when to get your ICTO support team involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools to use</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/tools/</guid>
      <description>UvA Assessment Documentation - Online support for UvA lecturers on taking assignments and assessments online.  Instructions &amp; Download   Find out more here.   Canvas assessments - Online tool for submission and online grading of assessments.  Instructions &amp; Download   Here are the instructions to set up an assessment in Canvas.   Canvas Rubrics - Online grading grid used with a Canvas assessment. Helps to grade faster and more consistently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do this</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/why/</guid>
      <description>Learning to the test is common practice in student behavior (and human behavior). If that’s the case, it’s important to have the test meet your standards. At the same time, online practices require additional trustworthy procedures for both you, your students and the institution. Always contact your faculty’s ICTO support staff for more information about assessment tools (specifically for exams) available at your faculty. The ICTO team helps you in making the right technical choices and provides support before and during exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/remote-assessment-aid/medium/assessment/tips/</guid>
      <description>Peer-feedback increases the amount of feedback for students. Sidenote, it often doesn’t save the lecturer time as he/she has a different role to fulfill; providing feedback on the peer-feedback. If you leave out this part, students often tend to underestimate the value of peerfeedback and perceive it as ineffective additional work. A plenary Zoom session or pre-recorded video to discuss the best feedback and your general view on the products (main mistakes, issues, things to attend), helps to overcome these issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
