<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Office Hours on Educational Redesign Aid</title>
    <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Office Hours on Educational Redesign Aid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What to do</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/what/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/what/</guid>
      <description>Organise a live Zoom Q&amp;amp;A session on set times (1 hour per week). To attend to students individually, turn on the waiting room option, and let students in one-by-one. Alternatively, you can schedule a Canvas Live-Chat session of 30-45 min for students to raise questions. Students can then review the questions and answers of other students too. Finally, you have the option of opening a Canvas Discussion Board for students to raise and upvote questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools to use</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/tools/</guid>
      <description>ZOOM - Online communication tool to provide live group sessions.  Instructions &amp; Download   Check out short instruction videos on how to schedule a Zoom session in Canvas, the basics of Zoom (made by Fam te Poel, UvA TLC). Full instructions can be found here.   CANVAS Discussion Board and Live Chat - Online tools to facilitate lecturer-student and student-student interaction in-between classes.  Instructions &amp; Download   Check out the instructions on how to set up Discussions or a Live Chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do this</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/why/</guid>
      <description>Online teaching requires more effort to stay connected to your students. In addition, students may feel disconnecting to the university, the program, and their fellow students. Students may experience different kinds of issues like lack of facilities, stamina, or social competencies to thrive in an online learning environment. Organising short Live Chat sessions or opening up a Discussion Board and responding on set times, helps to increase the sense of belonging, support and your accessibility to your students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/small/office_hours/tips/</guid>
      <description>Add a personal start of the week (video) message with Kaltura in Canvas to announce the topics of the week and address (upvoted) questions based on the Discussion Board. This can be a way to quickly address all issues and personalize your interaction with more students at once. Provide a Zoom office session or a Canvas Live Chat shortly after a lecture, seminar or workgroup. Students are often still in a learning mode and may have questions they don’t want to address in the general Zoom session (like in an offline setting).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
