<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guest Lectures on Educational Redesign Aid</title>
    <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guest Lectures on Educational Redesign Aid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/what/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/what/</guid>
      <description>Record a one-on-one interview using Zoom. Aim for a maximum interview of 30-45 minutes. If possible, cut the recording in segments based on (sub)topics of 15 min max. Upload the interview to Canvas for viewing as part of structured self-study. Add clear instructions for your students. For example, indicate when students should watch it, add a question, what to look for and/or and what they should be able to do or know afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do this</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/why/</guid>
      <description>With large groups, a live Zoom session is less feasible. Students might encounter technical problems which prevent them from (completely) following a live session and there are limits to the number of students that can participate in a Zoom-session. Therefore pre-recorded lectures are the way to go.
Ideally, your students watch the (full) interview in a ‘learning mode’ (active processing) instead of a ‘watching tv mode’ (passive processing). This may take up a lot of your students’ energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/guest_lectures/tips/</guid>
      <description>Add a cliff-hanger to the first interview. For example, if your guest has a real life example, don’t tell the end of the story until the second interview. Add a short quiz to your video with Feedback Fruits. For example, to assess students’ understanding of the subject matter, to have your guest raise a question, or to have students think about what they would do in a real life example before your guest continues a story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>