<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Individual Assignments on Educational Redesign Aid</title>
    <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Individual Assignments on Educational Redesign Aid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What to do</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/what/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/what/</guid>
      <description>Appropriate assignments depend on a range of factors, including the subject matter, content complexity, course level and the number of students enrolled. There are many options to consider, such as short response papers, quizzes, adjusted field work and problem solving assignments. The same goes for assessment formats. Typically, they include essays, reports, presentations, skills tests, open-ended or multiple choice exams. We recommend that you review our Assessments Documentation to learn more about the digital varieties for each of the assignment and assessment options, and then determine what is most appropriate for your course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools to use</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/tools/</guid>
      <description>UvA Assessment Documentation - Online support for UvA lecturers on taking assignments and assessments online.  Instructions &amp; Download   Find out more here.   Canvas Assignments - Online tool for submission and online grading of assignments.  Instructions &amp; Download   Here are the instructions to set up an assignment in Canvas.   Canvas Rubrics - Online grading grid used with a Canvas Assignment. Helps to grade faster and more consistently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do this</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/why/</guid>
      <description>Clear assignments with useful feedback during a course are one of the most effective educational tools you have to teach your students. In both online and offline settings, assignments with feedback 1) provide an opportunity for your students to practice and to process the subject matter (students’ learning), 2) help your students to determine whether they are on track or should adjust what and how they are studying (students’ self-regulation), and 3) provide you with necessary information on your students’ understanding, progress and content related difficulties (teaching regulation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tlc-uva.github.io/educational-redesign-aid/large/individual_assignments/tips/</guid>
      <description>If you have more students working on the same individual assignments, consider adding peer-feedback with Feedback Fruits. Peer-feedback increases the amount of feedback for students. Sidenote, it often doesn’t save the lecturer time as he/she has a different role to fulfill; providing feedback on the peer-feedback. If you leave out this part, students often tend to underestimate the value of peerfeedback and perceive it as ineffective additional work. A plenary Zoom session or pre-recorded video to discuss the best feedback and your general view on the products (main mistakes, issues, things to attend), helps to overcome these issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
